明白吗？
You understand?
你有男朋友吗？不，你没有男朋友
You got a boyfriend? No, you ain't got a boyfriend.
你可曾想过没有男朋友的原因？
You know why? Why don't you think you have a boyfriend?
因为你和街上的痞子鬼混
'Cause you're hangin' out with them coconuts on the corner.
和痞子鬼混没出息
You hang around coconuts, you get nowhere.
他们一无是处
They're lemons. Lemons.
与好人交往就会有好的朋友
You hang out with nice people, you get nice friends. You understand?
与聪明人交往就会有聪明的朋友
You hang out with smart people, you get smart friends.
与混混交往就会有混混朋友
You hang out with yo-yo people, you get yo-yo friends.
这个道理很简单
You see, it's simple mathematics.
我希望你不会…我不会
- I hope you ain't... - I won't.
我说的重点是？
What was I gonna say?